inateck.com 2018-06-27

# Inateck - Privacy Policy

**Data-Protection Statement and Consent to Use of Data at inateck.com**  
Data protection is a matter of trust and your trust is important to us. So that you can feel secure when visiting our websites, we strictly observe the statutory regulations in processing your person-specific data and we would like to inform you here about our data acquisition and data utilization. The following data-protection statement explains to you which data is collected from you on our websites, which parts of this data we process and use and in which way, and to whom you can turn with any concerns or requests. 

You can request, at any time and free of charge, information about your data stored by us, and can exercise your right to correction, blockage or deletion of your data.

**1\. Acquisition, Processing and Utilization of Person-Specific Data**  
Person-specific data describes details relating to the actual or personal relationships of a specific or identifiable natural person. Such details include, for example, your name, your telephone number, your address, and all existing data that you disclose to us during registration and when opening your customer account.  
 ****

**1.1 Customer Account**

****For each customer who registers with us via the REGISTER function, we set up a customer account, i.e. password-protected, direct access to his or her existing data stored by us. This allows you, amongst other things, to view your already-concluded, still open and recently sent orders, or to manage your personal data and the newsletter.

**1.1.1 Setup of the Customer Account**  
The following data must be given during the registration for a customer account (obligatory disclosures):  
– your e-mail address  
– your password  
– your forename  
– your first name  
– your last name  
– consent to the sign up for newsletter(optional)  
Your billing and delivery address need not be given until you order something. For your order we need your correct name, address and payment data. We need your e-mail address so that we can confirm receipt of your order and its dispatch, and so that we can communicate with you in general. We also use your first name and last name to identify you (as a log-in name), when you visit your customer account.

**1.1.2. Use of the Customer Account**  
You can use your Inateck customer account to log-in to the various online stores, including US site inateck.com, UK site https://www.inateck.com/uk/ , German site https://www.inateck.com/de/, Italian site https://www.inateck.com/it/, French site https://www.inateck.com/fr/ and Japanese site https://www.inateck.com/jp/.If you do not log out of your customer account, you will automatically remain logged in.

**1.2 Acquisition, Processing and Utilization of Your Person-Specific Data**

We collect, store and process your data for the entire processing of your purchase, the technical administration, our own marketing purposes (more information on these under point 2.3) and to prevent criminal offences and fraud. Your person-specific data is only passed on to third parties to the extent that this is legally permissible, including the purpose of processing the contract or for invoicing, for marketing or if you have previously consented to this. When processing orders, for example, the service companies used by us (transport companies, logistics companies, Paypal) are sent the data they require for processing and concluding orders. The data passed on to our service providers in this context may only be used by them for fulfilling their duties.

**1.3 Newsletter**  
For sending the Newsletter we make use of the e-mail address given by you and for this we need your confirmation that, as the owner of the e-mail address, you consent to its receipt .  
Should you later decide that you no longer want to receive a newsletter from us, you can object to this at any time without thereby incurring any other costs. There is, of course, also a cancellation link in every newsletter.

**2\. Cookies**

The acceptance of cookies is not a prerequisite for access to our websites. We draw your attention, however, to the fact that our website and service has only limited functionality, if you do not allow us to place cookies.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small files that are stored on your data carrier and hold certain settings and data for exchange with our system via your browser. Basically speaking there are 2 different types of cookies: the so-called session cookies, that are deleted as soon as you close your browser; and temporary/permanent cookies, that are stored on your data carriers for a longer period or without limit. This type of storage helps us to design our websites and our offers for you and makes it easier for you to use them in that, for example, certain input from you can be stored so that you are not required to enter this repeatedly.

**  
****How we use cookies**

****We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  
• Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes  
• If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@inateck.com  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the General Data Protection Regulation 2018. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**What data is stored in the cookies?**  
In the cookies used by Inateck, only pseudonymous data is stored. On activation of the cookie this is allocated an identification number; an allocation of your person-specific data to this identification number is not undertaken. Your name, your IP address and other such data that might allow the cookie to be traced to you directly are not placed in the cookie. On the basis of the cookie technology we receive only pseudonymized information, relating for example to which of our shop pages have been visited, which products were viewed, etc.

**Are there also cookies from third-party suppliers (so-called "third-party cookies")?**  
Inateck makes use of a number of web partners who help to make the Internet offer and the websites more interesting for you. These cookies are temporary/permanent cookies that are deleted automatically after the pre-specified period. These temporary or even permanent cookies (lifespan of 14 days to 10 years) are stored on your hard disk and delete themselves after the pre-specified period. The cookies of our partner companies also contain solely pseudonymous - mostly even anonymous - data.

**3\. Log Files**  
With each access to the pages of Inateck usage data is transmitted by the respective Internet browser and is stored in record files, the so-called server log files. The records stored in this way contain the following data: date and time of the call-up, name of the page called up, IP address, referrer URL (URL of origin, from which you came to the websites), the quantities of data transferred, product information and the version of the browser used.These log file data records are evaluated by us, to help us further improve our offer and the Inateck site, as well as to make these more-user-friendly, to detect and correct errors more quickly and to control server capacities.

**4\. Google Analytics**  
In order to constantly improve and optimize our offer, we make use of so-called tracking technologies. For this purpose we enlist the services of Google Analytics.

This website makes use of Google (Universal) Analytics, a web-analysis service from Google Inc. (www.google.com). Google (Universal) Analytics deploys methods that make it possible to analyze the use made of the website by you, e.g. the so-called "cookies", which are text files that are stored on your computer. The information generated on your use of this website is transmitted, as a rule, to a Google server in the USA and stored there. By activating the IP-anonymize function on this website the IP address is shortened, within the member countries of the European Union or in other contracting states that were party to the agreement on the European Economic Area, before further transfer. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address sent to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. The anonymized IP address transferred by your browser within the framework of Google Analytics is not brought together with other Google data.

You can prevent the acquisition of the data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (incl. your IP address) by Google, as well as its processing by Google.  
Google Analytics on this website in the future. In this case an opt-out cookie will be placed in your terminal device.

**5\. Re-Targeting and Data Acquisition by Third Parties**  
In the context of re-targeting, make use of the services of Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA;   
<https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy>

**6\. Social Plug-Ins**  
This Internet presentation makes use of a social plug-in from Facebook (Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA) on several pages only. This plug-in is normally deactivated and therefore sends no data. With a click on the plug-in, you can activate the plug-in. The plug-ins can be deactivated again by clicking in the same place again.  
When this plug-in is activated, your browser makes a direct connection to the Facebook servers as soon as you call up a website containing this plug-in. The content of the plug-in is transmitted directly from Facebook to your browser and is integrated by this in the website.

With the activation of the plug-in Facebook is informed that you have called up the corresponding page of our Internet presentation. If you are logged in with the social network, this can assign the visit to your account.

For the purpose and extent of the data acquisition and further processing and utilization of the data by Facebook and your rights in this connection and the setting options for protection of your private sphere, please refer to the data-protection information provided by Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy) .

YOUR USE OF OUR SITE MEANS THAT YOU ARE ACCEPT THE PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THIS POLICY. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES TO THE POLICY BY POSTING THE NEW VERSION WITH A NEW EFFECTIVE DATE. YOUR CONTINUED USE INDICATES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE CHANGES.
